songtrust.com 2017-04-04

# Songtrust - Terms of Service

Effective as of December 8, 2010

Because we care about the privacy of your information, we provide this Privacy Policy (this "Policy") to explain what information we collect about you online and what we may do with that info. The Policy applies to the websites www.songtrust.com (the "Sites"), which are owned and operated by ST Music LLC (“we” or “us”). The Policy doesn’t apply to information you may provide to us in person or by any other means. 

We reserve the right to modify the Policy at any time, and we will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Policy here and changing the "Effective Date" at the top of the page. Therefore, we encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes. By visiting any of the Sites, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy, as may be amended from time to time. Personal and other information collected on the Sites is stored and processed in the United States of America - by using any of the Sites, you consent to our collection, transfer to (if applicable), and use and processing of such information in the U.S.A. If you do not agree to these terms, please navigate away from the Sites and do not make any purchases or provide us with any personal information about you. 

### What information do we collect?

We generally collect two kinds of information from visitors to the Sites – some is personal information that you provide to us, and some is anonymous, non-personally identifiable information.

In order for you to receive promotional correspondence from us, to participate in contests or receive special offers, or to make purchases through the Sites, we may ask you to provide us with personal information such as your name, age, e-mail address, street address and telephone number. To facilitate online purchases, we also collect credit card information from you. We generally collect this personal information on our registration and order forms when you sign up to receive products or services from any of the Sites. From time to time, we may also collect information from our online surveys such as gender and income level.

We also may collect non-personal information about you and your use of the Sites. Such info may include log data such as your IP address, browser type and demographic information such as your zip code or location, and may use this data to: tailor your experience at the Sites; provide content in which we think you may be interested; display content according to your preferences and location; and analyze traffic to the Sites. Such information may be combined with your personally identifiable information. 

Like many sites, we may also use "cookies" to collect Site usage data and to improve the Sites. A “cookie” is a small data file transferred to your computer for access on future visits to the Sites. You can stop accepting cookies by setting your Internet browser accordingly, but this will likely result in our not recognizing you or your preferences on future visits, so you may have to re-enter your information.

### What do we do with the information we collect?

We may maintain and use the personal and other information you provide to us to fulfill your order or respond to your questions or comments, to provide you with information about us and the goods and services that we offer, to provide you with information from or about carefully-selected third parties that we think may interest you, and to contact you if necessary.

We use IP addresses and anonymous demographic information to tailor your experiences at the Sites by showing content in which we think you will be interested and displaying content according to your preferences. Anonymous demographic information may be shared with business partners, advertisers and/or others on an aggregate basis.

We may also use your feedback, Site usage data, and other information collected to evaluate and improve the Sites and the goods and services we offer.

### Do we share the information we collect with third parties?

We may share information we collect with our affiliated companies and/or with third parties whose products or services we think may interest you. We may also occasionally share information with business partners in connection with co-promotions, sweepstakes or contests on the Sites.

We may engage trusted third party service providers to perform functions and provide services to us, such as hosting and maintaining our servers and the Sites, database storage and management, e-mail marketing, credit card processing, customer service and fulfilling orders for products and services you may purchase through the Sites. We may share your personal information with these third parties to enable them to perform these services for us and for you.

Our policy is to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. Therefore, we may disclose information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect our rights and interests or those of a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to otherwise comply with applicable court orders, laws, rules and regulations.

### Is your information secure?

We are very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality and use of your personal information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. All credit transactions occur in a secure area of the Site using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") software to process orders, which encrypts the information you input on the Sites. In addition, all information is stored in a secure location behind a firewall with limited administrative access. However, please be aware that despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

Please be aware that any information or material you may enter in a publicly viewable portion of the Sites, such as an online forum or comment section, chat room, or bulletin board, will be readily accessible to the general public. Therefore, you obviously should not enter in those areas of the Site any personal information (e.g., your name, email or postal address, credit card details) or other information or materials that you would not wish to be publicly available and beyond the scope of this Policy.

### Does this Policy apply to linked sites other than the Sites?

No. The Sites may contain advertisements and links to other websites. The fact that we link to another site is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. Other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, and collect or solicit both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information from you under rules different from this Policy. We do not control other sites and can’t be responsible for your experience once you leave our Sites. Therefore, we strongly encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies, terms of use and other policies of other sites you visit.

### What is your policy regarding children’s information?

The Sites are not intended for, and we do not knowingly accept collect personally identifiable information from, children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete it from our files. If parents or guardians become aware that their minor children have provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent (or that we have otherwise collected or obtained such information), they should contact us at [help@songtrust.com](mailto:help@songtrust.com). We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask their parents for permission before using a credit card or providing any information about themselves to us or anyone else over the Internet. 

### How do I unsubscribe or update/correct my information?

Any promotional e-mails you receive from us will include specific instructions on how to unsubscribe from our e-mail list, and you may unsubscribe at any time. You may also send an email to us at: [cancellation@songtrust.com](mailto:cancellation@songtrust.com) to update or correct the personal information we have on file for you or to be unsubscribed from all or any particular types of e-mailings.

California residents may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [legal@songtrust.com](mailto:help@songtrust.com) or write to us at [485 Broadway, 3rd Floor New York, NY 10013], Attn: [Joe Conyers]. California residents who have an established business relationship with us may also choose to opt-out of our disclosing personal information about them to third parties. If you do not want us to share your personal information with such third parties, please send us your name, address and phone number to legal@songtrust.com.
